pewdiepie.net 2017-08-06

# | PewDiePie

Revelmode’s mission is to enable creators to share their passion for gaming and pop culture with you through unique shows, games, charitable programs, community events and other activities. Revelmode’s sites and Applications are not intended for individuals under the age of 13. By using Revelmode’s sites and Applications you affirm that you are at least 13 years of age.

Our privacy policy is designed to provide transparency regarding Revelmode’s privacy practices and principles.

PXM Network Limited’s (“Revelmode”) Privacy Policy

Last Modified: October 6, 2016

This privacy policy describes the treatment of information provided or collected on the sites where this privacy policy is posted. It also explains the treatment of information provided or collected on Applications we make available on third-party sites or platforms if disclosed to you in connection with use of the Application. We follow this privacy policy in accordance with local law in the places where we operate. Definitions of capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy are provided at the bottom of this page.

1\. Types of Information We Collect

2\. How We Collect Your Information

3\. Use of Your Information by Revelmode and Related Companies

4\. Sharing Your Information with Other Companies

5\. Online Tracking and Advertising

6\. Your Controls and Choices

7\. Data Security, Integrity and Retention

8\. Data Transfers, Storage and Processing Globally

9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

10\. Comments and Questions

11\. Your California Privacy Rights

1\. Types of Information We Collect

We collect two basic types of information – Personal Information and Anonymous Information – and we may use personal and Anonymous Information to create a third type of information, Aggregate Information. We collect the following categories of information:

 Registration information you provide when you create an account, such as first name and surname, country of residence, gender, date of birth, email address, username and password

 Transaction information you provide when you request information or purchase a product or service from us, whether on our sites or through our Applications, including your postal address, telephone number and payment information

 Information you provide in Public Forums on our sites and Applications

 Information sent either one-to-one or within a limited group using our message, chat, post or

similar functionality, where we are permitted by law to collect this information

 Information you provide to us when you use our sites and Applications, our Applications on third-party sites or platforms such as social networking sites, or link your profile on a third-party site or platform with your registration account

 Location information when you visit our sites or use our Applications, including location information either provided by a mobile device interacting with one of our sites or Applications, or associated with your IP Address, where we are permitted by law to process this information

 Usage, viewing and technical data, including your device identifier or IP Address, when you visit our sites, use our Applications on third-party sites or platforms or open emails we send

2\. How We Collect Your Information

 We collect information you provide to us when you request products, services or information from us, register with us, participate inPublic Forumsor other activities on our sites and Applications, respond to customer surveys, or otherwise interact with us. When you provide information to us on a third-party site or platform (for example, via our Applications), the information you provide may be separately collected by the third-party site or platform. The information we collect is covered by this privacy policy and the information the third-party site or platform collects is subject to the third-party site or platform’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the third-party site or platform will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly through our Applications.

 We collect information through technology, such as cookies, Flash cookies and Web beacons, including when you visit our sites and Applications or use our Applications on third-party sites or platforms. Please see the Section regarding Your Online Tracking and Advertising for more information.

 We acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically. Local law may require that you authorize the third party to share your information with us before we can acquire it.

3\. Use of Your Information by Revelmode and Related Companies

Revelmode is the data controller for your information. Revelmode may share your data with its Related Companies, The Walt Disney Family of Companies and PewDie Productions UK Limited, unless prohibited under applicable law, for the following purposes:

 Provide you with the products and services you request

 Communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information

about features on our sites and Applications or changes to our policies

 Consistent with local law and choices and controls that may be available to you:

o Send you offers and promotions for our products and services or third-party products and services

o Personalize content and experiences on our sites and Applications

o Provide you with advertising based on your activity on our sites and Applications and on third-party sites and applications. To learn more about how we use your information for personalization and tracking, please the Section regarding Online Tracking and Advertising.

 Optimize or improve our products, services and operations

 Detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal

4\. Sharing Your Information with Other Companies

We will not share your Personal Information outside Revelmode or its Related Companies except in limited circumstances, including:

 When you allow us to share your Personal Information with another company, such as:

o Electing to share your Personal Information with carefully selected companies so that

they can send you offers and promotions about their products and services

o Directing us to share your Personal Information with third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites

Please note that once we share your Personal Information with another company, the information received by the other company becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.

 When companies perform services on our behalf, like package delivery and customer service; however, these companies are prohibited from using your Personal Information for purposes other than those requested by us or required by law

 When we share Personal Information with third parties in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of Revelmode’s assets, to enforce our Terms of Use or rules, to ensure the safety and security of our users and third parties, to protect our rights and property and the rights and property of our users and third parties, to comply with legal process or in other cases if we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law

5\. Online Tracking and Advertising

We and certain service providers operating on our behalf may collect information about your activity on our sites and Applications using tracking technologies such as cookies, Flash cookies, and web beacons. This tracking data may be used for many purposes, including personalizing your experience with our products and services, such as displaying content based on your preferences, usage, and location. We may associate this tracking data with your registration account, in which case we will treat it as Personal Information.

Advertisers and third parties also may collect information about your activity on our sites and Applications and on third-party sites and applications using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these advertisers and third parties is used to decide which ads you see both on our sites and Applications and on third-party sites and applications, but does not identify you personally and is not associated with your registration account.

Examples of online tracking technologies include:

 Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use cookies to bring together information we collect about you. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

 Flash cookies. We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.

 Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use web beacons to bring together information we collect about you.

We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

Do Not Track is a standard that is currently under development. As it is not yet finalized, we adhere to the standards set out in this privacy policy. Learn about Do Not Track.

6\. Your Controls and Choices

We provide you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding our collection, use and sharing of your information. In accordance with local law, your controls and choices may include:

 You may correct, update and delete your registration account

 You may change your choices for subscriptions, newsletters and alerts

 You may choose whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to you

 You may choose whether we share your Personal Information with other companies so they can send you offers and promotions about their products and services

 You may choose whether to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers here

 You may also choose to control targeted advertising you receive within Applications by using your mobile device settings (for example, by resetting your device’s advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads).

 You may request access to the Personal Information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it and we request third parties with whom we have shared the information do the same

You may exercise your controls and choices, or request access to your Personal Information, by contacting Customer Service, or following instructions provided in communications sent to you. Please be aware that, if you do not allow us to collect Personal Information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain products and services to you, and some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If you have questions regarding the specific Personal Information about you that we process or retain, please contact Customer Service.

7\. Data Security, Integrity and Retention

The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect customer information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We will

retain your Personal Information for the length of time needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

8\. Data Transfers, Storage and Processing Globally

We operate globally and may transfer your Personal Information to individual Related Companies or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this privacy policy. Wherever your Personal Information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information.

9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may change this privacy policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. We will provide Notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent.

10\. Comments and Questions

If you have a comment or question about this privacy policy, please contact Customer Service. Our sites and Applications may contain links to other sites not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our sites or Applications and to read the privacy policies of other sites that may collect your Personal Information.

11\. Your California Privacy Rights: If you are a California resident, you may have certain additional rights. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your Personal Information by Revelmode to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits registered users who are minors to request and obtain deletion of certain posted content. To make such a request, please send an email to privacy@revelmode.com or write us at:

Revelmode

c/o Maker Studios, Inc.

1976 S. La Cienega Blvd., #224 Los Angeles, CA 90034

Definitions

Aggregate Information. Aggregate information means information about groups or categories of users,

which does not identify and cannot reasonably be used to identify an individual user.

Anonymous Information.Anonymous Information means information that does not directly or indirectly identify, and cannot reasonably be used to identify, an individual user.

Application. Application means a program or service operated by us (or on our behalf) that may be displayed on various online, mobile or other platforms and environments, including those operated by third parties, which permits us to interact directly with our users.

Data Controller. The Data Controller is Revelmode (i.e., PXM Network Limited).

IP Address. An IP Address is associated with the access point through which you enter the Internet, and is typically controlled by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your company, or your university. We may use IP Addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our sites and Applications, and we may combine IP Addresses with Personal Information.

Notice. Notice may be by email to you at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on our sites and Applications, or by other means, consistent with applicable law.

Personal Information. Personal Information means information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, such as the individual’s name, postal address, email address and telephone number. When anonymous information is directly or indirectly associated with personal information, this anonymous information also is treated as Personal Information.

Public Forums. Our sites and Applications may offer message boards, conversation pages, blogs, chat rooms, social community environments, profile pages, and other forums that do not have a restricted audience. If you provide Personal Information when you use any of these features, that Personal Information may be publicly posted and otherwise disclosed without limitation as to its use by us or by a third party. To request removal of your Personal Information from a public forum on one of our sites or Applications, please contact Customer Service.

Related Companies. The Walt Disney Family of Companies and PewDie Productions UK Limited.

The Walt Disney Family of Companies. The Walt Disney Family of Companies refers to The Walt Disney Company and its subsidiary and affiliated entities, which offer their products and services under various brand names. These companies engage in a number of businesses, including theme parks and travel, motion pictures and television, publishing, consumer products and interactive services. The Walt Disney Company brands include, among others, the following:

 ABC

 Disney

 Disney Interactive

 Disney Pixar

 ESPN

 Hollywood Records

 Lucasfilm

 Maker Studios

 Marvel

 Star Wars

Customer Service Contact Information

Email: privacy@revelmode.com

Address: Revelmode

c/o Maker Studios, Inc.

1976 S. La Cienega Blvd., #224 Los Angeles, CA 90034
